(Sheldon:)who can't find love himself.
(Sheldon:)It's ironic, but the point is
(Sheldon:)we can't trust you.
(Sheldon:)You're a sketchy character
in a parking garage.
(Man:)Yeah, well,
from my perspective,
(Man:)that's how you two appear to me.
(Sheldon:)Well, I never thought
of it like that.
(Sheldon:)Boy, frame of reference will
just sneak up on you, won't it?
(Leonard:)My friend does make a decent
point about the money.
(Leonard:)I don't feel comfortable
just handing it over up front.
Ah-ah-ah, no money, no helium.
(Man:)Seems we're at a, uh, stalemate.
(Sheldon:)Not technically.
(Sheldon:)In chess, a stalemate
refers to a situation
(Sheldon:)in which there
are no remaining moves.
(Sheldon:)Uh, you have plenty
of moves available.
(Sheldon:)You could beat us up
and steal the money.
(Sheldon:)You could kill us,
you know.
(Sheldon:)Really, you're only limited
by your imagination.
(Sheldon:)Huh.
(Man:)All these years,
I've been using “stalemate,”
when I really mean “impasse.”
(Man:)I feel foolish.